A Guide to the Papers of Hugh Scott 1681-1917
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of Hugh Scott, 1681-1987
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
10200-ab
There are 11,000 items (ca. 17 linear feet) in this collection.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access to this collection is restricted to the general public until 1992. Upon removal of the access restrictions, permission for publication of material must be obtained from Scott of his designated personal representative.
Acquisition Information
This collection was given to the Library by the Honorable Hugh Scott of Falls Church, Virginia, on February 15, 1988.
Biographical/Historical Information
Hugh Scott was a U.S. Senator from Pennsylvania.
Scope and Content Information
These additional papers include personal, business, financial, and political correspondence and papers; invitations; manuscripts of papers and books by Scott; oral history interviews; photographs; newspaper clippings and other printed material; bound volumes; and memorabilia, concerning Scott's political career and his private endeavors as a collector of Chinese art. There is also a bronze bust of Senator Scott sculpted by William Thompson of Athens, Georgia.
Other items include seven letters, 1860 and 1864, to Thomas R. Ware, Purser of the United States Navy and Paymaster of the Confederate States Navy, chiefly concerning the pay of men. There is also a quit- claim or release, ca. 1681-1685, signed by William Penn (1644-1718), colonizer.
Organization
ORGANIZATION
I. Historical: Box 1
II. Topical: Boxes 1-17
III. Invitations: Boxes 18- 29
IV. Books by Hugh Scott: Boxes 29-36
V. Photographs: Boxes 36-40
Topical: Boxes 36-38
Hugh and Marian Scott: Boxes 38-40
VIPs: Box 40
Slides: Box 40
VI. Printed: Boxes 41-42
VII. Books: Box 42
VIII. Bound Volumes: Boxes 43-49
IX. Loose Bound Volumes (Oversize)
X. Bronze Bust of Hugh Scott
Index
The main finding aid to this collection is the listing. Use this index as a supplement to the listing, not as a replacement. The numbers following the entries refer to box number followed by folder numbers.
Adenauer, Konrad -- Photograph: 39.3
Advocates to Save Legal Services: 11.6
African Continent -- trips: 13.6
Agnew, Judy -- Photograph: 38.8, 39.3, 40.6
Agnew, Spiro T. -- Photograph: 39.4, 40.6
Albert, Carl: 21.5, 23.4, 25.4
Alexander, Lamar -- Photograph: 39.5
Allen, Richard V.: 4.3, 17.1, 27.2
Alpha Chi Rho -- Photograph: 39.1, 39.3
American Jewish Committee: 1.3
American Political System Lectures: 1.4
American Red Cross: 5.7
Angola: 3.4
Anne, Princess of Great Britain -- Photograph: 39.4
Annenberg, Leonore: 17.1
Arends, L. C.: 25.7
Asia--trips: 13.1- 13.5
Asian Continent--trips: 13.6
Atwater, Lee: 17.1
Austria--Vienna -- Photograph: 39.1, 39.5
Austria--Salzburg -- Photograph: 39.5
Baker, Howard H., Jr. -- Photograph: 40.7
Baker, Howard H., Jr.: 4.2, 11.7, 17.4
Baker, Milton Grafly: 18.5
Balliol College, Oxford, England: 8.6, 16.6
Barrett, Harold J., Jr.: 26.2
Bartlett, Joe: 27.5
Battle, Laurie C.: 4.8
Bayh, Birch: 22.2
Bayh, Marvella: 27.6
Bell, Alphonzo: 18.3
Bellmon, Henry: 22.1
Bennett, Marion T.: 4.8
Bentsen, Lloyd: 16.3
Berger, Samuel D.: 26.1
Beshany, P.A.: 16.7
Bice, Raymond C.: 22.3, 23.5, 24.1, 25.2
Biden, Joseph R., Jr.: 17.1
Biester, Edward G., Jr.: 17.1
Blackmun, Harry A.: 17.1
Blair, William McC., Jr.: 21.1
Blatt, Genevieve: 17.1
Blossom, Summer: 1.5
Boggs, J. Caleb: 4.8, 20.6
Bow Group: 11.3
Bradley, Dan J.: 11.6
Brezhnev, Leonid Illyich -- Photograph: 40.6
Brock, William E., III: 4.8, 17.1, 26.1, 26.4
Broderick, Raymond J.: 21.1
Brooke, Edward W.: 26.4
Brownson, Charles B.: 4.8
Bruno, Joseph C.: 24.3
Buckley, James L.: 4.8
Bunker, Ellsworth: 17.1
Burdick, Quentin N.: 17.1
Burnet, Alastair: 24.3
Bush, Barbara -- Photograph: 40.2
Bush, Barbara: 17.3
Bush, George -- Photograph: 40.2
Bush, George: 17.5, 24.5, 25.1, 25.3, 26.1, 26.5, 27.2
Butler, Caldwell: 22.3
Byrd, Harry F., Jr.: 21.6, 26.2
Cambodia--trips: 13.6
Campaign--contributions and honorariums: 2.1
Campaign--itinerary: 1.11, 1.12
Campaign-- voters' lists: 2.2
Canzeri, Joseph W.: 17.1
Capetown--trips: 13.6
Carmichael, Leonard: 5.7
Carter, Jimmy: 17.6
Case, Clifford P.: 18.5, 27.3
Cederberg, Elford A.: 17.1
Chaffee, John H.: 16.3, 22.4
Chamberlain, Bernard P.: 17.15
Charles, Prince of Wales -- Photograph: 39.4
China: 15.3
China--articles: 2.6, 2.7, 3.1
China--trips: 13.6, 14.1
Chinese Art: 3.2
Christensen, William H.: 3.7
Church, Frank--memorial: 8.7
Churchill, Winston S. -- memorial: 8.7
Churchill, Winston--conversation with, 7/44: 16.4
Civil Rights Act of 1963 Signing -- Photograph: 39.2
Civil War: 1.1
Clark, Joseph S. -- Photograph: 40.1
Clarke, Joseph A.: 18.2
Conable, Barber B., Jr.: 21.4
Concannon, Mary Michael -- Photograph: 38.11
Congressional--miscellaneous: 3.4
Contributions and honorariums--campaign 2.1
Cook, Marlow W. 22.2, 23.4, 26.3
Cooper, John Sherman -- Photograph: 39.4
Cooper, John Sherman: 4.2, 4.3, 4.4
Cotton, Norris: 21.3
Coughlin, Lawrence: 17.1
Cowen, Eugene S.: 11.8, 23.4
Crawford, Edwin M.: 26.2
Curtis, Thomas B.: 19.2
D'Amato, Alfonse M.: 4.3
Daddario, Emilio Q.: 4.8
Dalton, John N.: 17.1
Daniloff, Nicholas: 24.3
Danworth, John C.: 25.3
Davies, D.O.: 4.2, 4.4, 17.1
Democratic Conventions, 1789-1892: 4.5
Dewey, Thomas E.: 1.4, 17.1
Dirksen, Everett McKinley -- Photograph: 38.8, 39.2, 39.3, 39.7, 40.4
Dirksen, Everett McKinley: 18.4, 20.1
Distinguished Service Award: 4.8
Ditchley Foundation Conference: 14.3, 14.4
Dole, Elizabeth H -- Photograph: 40.7
Dole, Elizabeth H.: 17.1
Dole, Robert Joseph -- Photograph: 39.5, 40.7
Dole, Robert Joseph: 11.1, 17.1, 23.1, 23.5
Domenici, Pete V.: 24.3
Dominick, Peter H.: 21.1
Donovan, Hedley: 23.2
Dorsch, Betty -- Photograph: 39.2
Douglas, Paul H. -- Photograph: 40.1
Dulles, Eleanor Lansing: 17.1
Eagleton, Thomas F.: 16.3, 23.4
Eastland, James O.: 19.3
Eisenhower, Dwight David -- Photograph: 5.3, 40.3
Eisenhower, Dwight David: 17.3
Eisenhower, Mamie Doud: 17.1
Eisenhower, Mamie Doud -- Photograph: 38.8, 40.3
Elliott, W. Glenn: 21.6
England: 14.6, 14.7, 16.9
England--trips: 14.2-14.5
Ervin, Sam J., Jr.: 22.2, 26.2
Eun, Kim Sung (copy): 3.7
Europe and Asia--summary of trips: 15.1
Europe--trips: 13.2-13.5, 15.2
Fairbanks, Douglas, Jr.: 22.1
Faries, McIntyre: 4.3
Fiji--trips: 15.6
Flanagan, William R.: 16.8
Fong, Alice -- Photograph: 38.8
Ford, Betty - - Photograph: 38.8, 40.4
Ford, Betty: 5.7, 17.3
Ford, Gerald R. -- Photograph: 40.4, 40.6
Ford, Gerald R.: 17.3, 17.7, 27.2
Former Members of Congress: 4.8
Fox, Richard J.: 17.1
Frame, Richard C.: 23.4, 26.2, 27.2
Friedersdorf, Max L.: 4.3, 17.1
Fulbright, James W. -- Photograph: 39.2
Fulbright, James W.: 17.1
Georgian Soviet Socialist Republic--Tbilisi, Briefings -- Photograph: 40.1
Gidimo, Robert N.: 4.8
Gleason, Robert A., Jr.: 17.1
Goldwater, Barry: 21.1, 24.5
Goodell, Charles E.: 4.8
Green, Clifford Scott: 20.3
Griffin, Robert P.: 17.1
Grundy, Joseph R.: 3.7
Gulick, Arnon -- Photograph: 39.7
Hagin, Joseph W.: 17.1
Hammer, Armand: 4.1
Hanley, James M.: 4.8
Hansen, Clifford P.: 24.2
Hansen, George V.: 18.3
Hansen, Orval: 4.8
Harrison, Marion Edwyn: 17.1
Hart, Philip A.: 23.4
Hartmann, Robert Trowbridge: 17.1
Hatch, Orrin G.: 12.1
Hatfield, Antoinette -- Photograph: 38.8
Hatfield, Mark O.: 17.8, 18.4, 21.3
Hawaii--reservations: 13.2, 13.5
Hawaii--trips: 15.5
Hayden, Carl (copy): 3.7
Hearst, Randolph A.: 18.2
Hearst, Randolph A.: 23.4
Heinz, H. John: 3.4, 17.1
Helms, Jesse -- Photograph: 39.5
Hickenlooper, Bourke B.: 19.5
Hildenbrand, William F.: 11.7, 17.1, 27.3
Hill, Alice Mitchell (Scott) -- Photograph: 38.11
Ho, David: 4.1
Hong Kong--trips: 13.1, 13.3
Hooper, Edwin B.: 16.8
Hoover, J. Edgar: 3.7
Hosmer, Craig: 4.8
Hruska, Roman L.: 4.8
Hudson, Henry E.: 17.1
Hugh Scott Room -- Photograph: 39.5
Hugh Scott Room--dedication: 4.4
Hughes, Harold E.: 25.7
Hughes, Richard J.: 19.5
Humphrey, Gordon J.: 17.1
Humphrey, Hubert H. -- Photograph: 39.2
Humphrey, Hubert H.: 17.9, 19.3
Humphrey, Hubert H. (copy): 3.7
Humphrey, Muriel -- Photograph: 38.8
Humphrey, Muriel: 5.7
Hurley, Patrick Jay -- Photograph: 39.7
Iceland--Marine Corps: 16.4
India--trips: 13.6
Indonesia--trips: 15.3
Inter-Parliamentary Union/England: 14.5
Inter-Parliamentary Union/Monaco: 15.4
Inter-Parliamentary Union/Spain: 16.1
Inter-Parliamentary Union/USSR: 15.2
Inter-Parliamentary Union/Venezuela: 16.2
Interstate Highway System: 5.3
Iran--trips and photographs: 15.4
Irwin, Theodore: 1.5
Italy--trips: 13.4
Itinerary--campaign: 1.11, 1.12
Japan--trips: 13.3, 13.6
Javits, Jacob K.: 23.6, 26.1, 26.3, 27.5
Jay, Peter: 17.2
Johnson, Albert W.: 26.4
Johnson, Jed, Jr.: 4.8
Johnson, Lady Bird -- Photograph: 40.5
Johnson, Lyndon B. -- Photograph: 39.2, 40.5
Joint Economic Committee: 5.6
Jordan, B. Everett: 9.10, 19.5
Jubelirer, Robert C.: 17.2
Kennedy, Edward M. -- Photograph: 40.1
Kennedy, Edward M.: 17.10
Kennedy, John F.--Memorial: 8.7
Kennedy, Robert Francis-- Memorial: 8.7
Keough, Eugene J.: 4.8
Keyes, Frances Parkinson: 5.7
Khan, Sultan Muhammad: 21.5, 23.5, 24.1
Kissinger, Henry -- Photograph: 39.4, 40.6
Klein, Esther: 16.7
Knox, Frank: 2.5
Kohler, Saul: 4.2, 24.2
Kornegay, Horace R.: 4.8
Korologos, Tom C.: 20.5, 22.3, 26.4, 27.2
Kunkel, John C.: 19.3
Kunzig, Robert L.: 4.1, 17.2, 23.5
Ladies of the Senate: 5.7
Landon, Alf M.: 17.2
Le Compte, Karl M.: 10.2
Leahy, Patrick J.: 4.1
Lewis, Andrew L., Jr.: 17.2, 23.4
Linowitz, Sol M.: 17.2
Litchfield Auction Gallery: 4.2
Long, Russell B.: 18.2
Luce, Clare Booth: 17.2
Luce, Henry, III: 17.2
Magna Carta Ceremonies: 14.6, 14.7
Magnuson, Warren G.: 20.1
Mahon, George H.: 4.8
Malik, Hardit Saige: 3.7
Mandel, Marvin: 23.4
Mansfield, Maureen -- Photograph: 38.8, 40.1
Mansfield, Mike -- Photograph: 39.4, 39.7, 39.8, 40.1, 40.4, 40.6
Mansfield, Mike: 4.2, 17.2, 20.1, 25.4
Marks, Marc Lincoln: 17.2
Marsh, John O., Jr.: 17.2
Mathias, Charles Mc., Jr.: 12.1, 16.3, 17.11, 19.5, 21.5, 22.2, 24.3, 26.4
Matsunaga, Nobuo: 17.2
Maxwell, Robert: 17.2
McCall-Judson, Alan: 14.3
McCarthy, Eugene J.: 4.8
McCarthy, Richard D.: 4.8
McClory, Robert: 24.5
McConnell, Joseph H.: 26.3
McDade, Joseph M.: 23.5
McGee, Gale: 27.3
McKay, Ernest A.: 4.1, 4.3
Mellon, Richard K.: 3.7
Mellon, Richard K. -- Photograph: 39.2
Michel, Robert: 26.1
Middendorf, J. William II: 16.8
Middleditch, Leigh B., Jr.: 26.3
Miller, Jack R.: 25.1
Mimo-Cho Japan air crash: 16.5
Mink, Patricia A.: 26.1
Mink, Patsy T.: 4.8
Mitchell, John N.: 21.4
Moffett, George D.: 17.2
Monaco--trips: 15.4
Monagan, John S.: 4.8
Montefiore, Alan C. R. G.: 26.1
Moore, Arch A., Jr.: 20.3
Moreland, J. Earl: 17.2, 18.4
Morella, Connie: 4.3
Morocco-- trips: 15.4
Morton, Rogers -- Photograph: 39.4
Morton, Rogers: 27.3
Morton, Thruston B.: 19.5
Moss, Frank E.: 19.1
Moynihan, Daniel Patrick: 16.3
Murphy, George: 19.3
Nakayama, Admiral -- Photograph: 39.2
Native Americans--Colorado -- Photograph: 39.1
Native Americans-- New Mexico -- Photograph: 39.1
Navy Department: 3.7
New Zealand--trips: 15.5, 15.6
Newcomer, Clarence C.:
Nixon, Patricia -- Photograph: 5.7, 38.8, 40.6
Nixon, Patricia: 17.3
Nixon, Richard M. -- Photograph: 39.4, 40.6
Nixon, Richard M.: 17.2, 17.3, 22.2
Northern Virginia Sun: "Otherwords": 9.1
O'Brian, Hugh: 26.1
O'Brien, George M.: 17.2, 27.2
O'Neil, Robert M.: 4.3
O'Neill, Thomas P., Jr. "Tip" -- Photograph: 40.6
Obermayer, Herman J.: 9.1, 17.2
Okawara, Yoshio: 20.3
Oral History Interviews--Hugh Scott: 9.2, 9.3
Osborne, Robert B.: 16.8
Owen, Chris: 9.7
Pacific Ocean--trips: 15.5, 15.6
Pacific Rim: 9.4
Packard, Vance: 1.5
Packwood, Bob: 24.4
Pakistan--Islamabad -- Photograph: 39.6
Panayotacos, C. P.: 26.4
Peabody, Robert L.: 12.2
Pearson, James B.: 25.4
Pell, Claiborne: 16.3
Penn, William: 1.2
Percy, Charles H.: 16.3, 17.2, 23.1
Perkins, Curtis T.: 23.2
Pirnie, Alexander: 20.1
Political--miscellaneous: 3.4
Pressler, Larry: 16.3, 17.2
Quigley, James M.: 4.8
Randolph, Jennings: 19.3, 20.6, 24.5
Randolph-Macon College: 9.9
Rayburn, Sam: 3.5, 3.6
Reagan, Nancy -- Photograph: 38.8
Reagan, Ronald -- Photograph: 40.7
Reed, Charles L., Jr.: 17.2
Rees, Thomas M.: 4.8
Reeves, Albert L., Jr.: 4.8
Republican Congressional Wives: 9.10
Residences of the Scotts: 11.5
Reuss, Henry S.: 5.6
Rickover, Hyman G.: 16.7, 16.8
Ripley, S. Dillon -- Photograph: 39.2
Ripley, S. Dillon 4.1, 17.2, 20.3, 20.4, 21.3, 23.2, 23.4, 24.3, 25.1, 26.3
Ripon Society: 11.3
Rizzo, Frank L.: 27.4
Robb, Charles S.: 17.2, 23.3
Rockefeller, Blanchette: 17.2
Rockefeller, Happy -- Photograph: 38.8, 40.1
Rockefeller, Happy: 5.7, 17.3
Rockefeller, John D., III: 15.3
Rockefeller, Nelson A. -- Photograph: 38.8, 40.1, 40.4
Rockefeller, Nelson A.: 17.2, 18.1
Rockefeller, Nelson Aldrich--memorial: 8.7
Rogers, Frank W.: 2.5
Rogers, Paul G.: 4.8
Romney, George -- Photograph: 39.7
Roosevelt, Franklin D., Jr. (copy): 3.7
Roth, Robert: 23.5
Roth, William V., Jr.: 27.3
Ruppe, Philip E.: 4.8
Rusk, Dean 17.1
Rusk, Dean (copy): 3.7
Sacasa, Guillermo Sevilla: 17.2
Saltonstall, Leverett (copy): 3.7
Saxbe, William B.: 25.4, 25.6
Saylor, John P.: 21.5
Schlesinger, Arthur: 5.6
Schneebeli, Herman T.: 20.1
Schneebeli, Herman T.--memorial: 8.7
Schweiker, Richard S. -- Photograph: 39.4
Schweiker, Richard S.: 17.2, 19.3, 19.5, 20.1, 26.4
Schwengel, Frederick D.: 4.8
Scott, Hugh--biographical: 1.8
Scott, Hugh--portrait: 9.7
Scott, Marian Huntington Chase: 12.7, 16.9
Scott, Marian Huntington Chase--"autobiography": 1.7
Scott, Marian Huntington Chase-- biographical: 1.9
Scott, Marian Huntington Chase--essays: 17.17
Scott, Marian Huntington Chase -- Photograph: 5.7
Scott, Marnie -- Photograph: 38.11
Scott, Marnie: 3.7
Scranton, William W. -- Photograph: 39.2
Scranton, William W.: 2.5, 18.5
Seidman, L. William: 4.2
Selden, Armistead I., Jr.: 4.8
Senate Appropriations Subcommittee on State, etc.: 11.6
Senate Bicentenary: 11.7
Senate Bicentennial Study Group: 11.7
Senate Ethics Committee: 11.8
Senate Joint Resolution 71: 12.1
Senate Judiciary Subcommittee on the Constitution: 12.1
Senate Resolution 381: 11.7
Shannon, Edgar F., Jr.: 2.5, 17.15, 21.2, 21.6, 23.3
Shimada, Lt. Gen. -- Photograph: 39.2
Shultz, George P.: 17.2
Sibal, Abner W.: 4.8
Sikes, Bob: 19.3
Skinner, Edith -- Photograph: 39.2
Smathers, George A.: 4.8
Smith, H. Alexander: 10.2
Smith, Margaret Chase -- Photograph: 38.8, 39.3, 40.4
Smith, Margaret Chase: 17.2
Smithsonian Institution: 12.3, 12.4, 24.3
Smithsonian Institution Board of Regents -- Photograph: 39.2
Snyder, Richard A.: 17.2
South Vietnam--Trips: 13.6
Spain--trips: 13.4, 15.7, 15.8
Specter, Arlen -- Photograph: 39.5
Specter, Arlen: 2.3, 16.3, 17.12
Speeches: 12.5, 12.6
Spong, William B., Jr.: 26.4
Springer, William L.: 4.3
St. George, Katherine Price Collier: 10.2
Staats, Elmer B.: 11.8
Stark, George L.: 1.5
Stennis, John C.: 11.8, 26.2
Stevens, Ted: 17.13, 21.1, 22.1
Stoessel, Walter J., Jr.: 17.2
Stover, Carl: 22.3
Strausz-Hupe, Robert: 27.4
Sullivan, John L.: 2.5
Swigert, John L., Jr.: 17.2
Symington, James W.: 4.8
Symington, Stuart: 4.8, 23.4
Taft, Robert, Jr.: 4.8, 18.1
Tahiti--trips: 15.5, 15.6
Talcott, Burt L.: 4.8
"Teas and Towels": 12.7
Thailand--trips: 13.3
Thompson, Kenneth W.: 4.1
Thornburgh, Richard L.: 17.14
Thurmond, Strom -- Photograph: 39.5
Thurmond, Strom: 24.5, 27.1
Timmons, William E.: 27.3
Tobey, Charles W.: 10.2
Tower, John -- Photograph: 39.7
Tower, John G.: 23.2, 24.4
Trescher, Robert L.: 19.6
Trips: 13.1-13.6
Trips: 14.1-14.8
Trips: 15.1-15.8
Trips: 16.1- 16.2
Tunisia -- Photograph: 15.4
Tunisia--trips: 15.4
Tunney, John V.: 26.2
Turk, James C.: 21.6
Turkey--trips: 13.5
Tuttle, Elbert P.: 17.2
Tydings, Joseph D.: 4.8, 18.2
U.S. Navy: 16.4, 16.5
U.S. Navy Air Crash at Mimo-Cho, Japan: 16.5
U.S. Political System Lectures: 16.6
U.S.-Japanese Government Leaders: 16.3
U.S.S. Mount Olympus--history: 16.4
U.S.S. Philadelphia--keel laying: 16.7, 16.8
Union of Soviet Socialist Republics--trips: 15.2
University of Virginia: 22.3, 22.4, 23.3, 24.1, 26.1
"Ups and Dons in Wary Old England": 16.9
V.I.P. Correspondence: 17.1-17.14
Valeo, Francis R.: 2.1, 4.2, 11.8
Van Sant, John T.: 27.7
Van Zandt, James E.: 4.8
Vance, Cyrus R.: 17.2
Venezuela--trips: 16.2
Virginia Museum of Fine Arts: 17.15
Voters' lists--campaign: 2.2
Walsh, Ira P.: 23.4, 25.7
Ware, John H., III: 4.8, 18.1
Ware, Thomas R.: 1.1
Warner, John W.: 16.3, 16.7
Warren, Earl -- Photograph: 39.2
Weicker, Lowell P., Jr.: 17.2, 18.1, 26.2
Weiner, Charles R.: 26.4
Whalley, J. I.: 26.4
White, Luther W., III: 21.6, 25.7
Whitehurst, Ben: 10.2
Whitten, Jamie L.: 27.5
Whittlesey, Faith Ryan: 4.1
Wilks, William L.: 4.2
William Randolph Hearst Foundation: 23.4
Williamsburg II: 15.3
Williamsburg VII: 3.4
Wilson, Richard L.: 21.2
Wolf, Elias: 20.3
Woman's Medical College of Pennsylvania: 17.16
Wyatt, Wendell: 18.4
Wyatt, Wendell: 23.6
Yaqub-Khan, Sahalzada: 27.2
Yoshihashi, Lt. Gen. -- Photograph: 39.2
Young, Milton R.: 26.2
Younger, Eric E.: 25.4
Your Senator's Reports: 17.18
Youth for Understanding: 17.19
Yugoslavia--trips: 13.2, 13.5
Zemin, Chai: 17.2
Zia, Mohammad Zia ul-Haq (President of Pakistan) -- Photograph: 39.5
Contents List
- HISTORICAL
  - Letters to Thomas R. Ware, Purser U.S.N. and Paymaster, C.S.N. 1860, 1864 (Box 1)
  - Quit-claim or Release, signed by William Penn ca. 1681-1685 (Box 1)
- TOPICAL
  - American Jewish Committee 1980-1983 (Box 1)
  - The American Political System Lectures, Princeton University, Princeton, New Jersey--delivered by Thomas E. Dewey 1950 (Box 1)
  - Articles by Hugh Scott, with related correspondence 1947-1979, n.d. (Box 1)
  - Associations 1979-1987 (Box 1)
  - "Autobiography" by Marian Huntington Chase Scott 1948 (Box 1)
  - Biographical Information on Hugh Scott 1963-1976 (Box 1)
  - Biographical Information on Marian Huntington Chase Scott 1967, n.d. (Box 1)
  - Budget--Personal 1974 (Box 1)
  - Campaign: Itinerary 1970, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Campaign: Statements of Contributions and Honorariums 1968-1975 (Box 2)
  - Campaign: Voters' Lists 1968-1970 (Box 2)
  - Campaign Fundraiser for Arlen Specter 1983 (Box 2)
  - Campaigns and Elections--General 1940-1982 (Box 2)
  - Certificates and Honors presented to Hugh Scott 1918-1982 (Box 2)
  - China Articles 1972-1980 (Box 2)
  - China Articles n.d (Box 2)
  - China Articles n.d. (Box 3)
  - Chinese Art 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Christmas Cards 1974-1975 (Box 3)
  - Congressman Sam Rayburn by Anthony Champagne 198[ ], 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Correspondence: Personal 1937-1969 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence: Personal 1970-1983 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence: Personal 1984 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence: Personal 1985-1987 (Box 4)
  - Currency: Domestic, Foreign, and Military ca. 1862-1969 (Box 4)
  - Dedication of the Hugh Scott Room 1981 (Box 4)
  - Democratic Conventions post 1892 (Box 4)
  - Favorite Miscellanea 1941-1976, n.d. (Box 4)
  - Financial Disclosures for Hugh Scott 1968-1975 (Box 4)
  - Former Members of Congress Project sponsored by Gale McGee and Hugh Scott, and related 1982 (Box 4)
  - Inauguration Ceremonies 1953-1965 (Box 4)
  - Inauguration Ceremonies 1969 (Box 5)
  - Inauguration Ceremonies 1973-1985 (Box 5)
  - Interstate Highway System 1955, 1986 (Box 5)
  - Invitation Lists 1945-1977 (Box 5)
  - Invitations Sent to Marian Huntington Chase Scott 1955-1976 (Box 5)
  - Joint Economic Committee 1982 (Box 5)
  - Ladies of the Senate 1958-1976 (Box 5)
  - Leadership Meeting Notes 1969, 3 folders (Box 6)
  - Leadership Meeting Notes 1970, 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Leadership Meeting Notes 1971 (Box 6)
  - Leadership Meeting Notes 1972 (Box 7)
  - Leadership Meeting Notes 1973, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Leadership Meeting Notes 1974, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Leadership Meeting Notes 1975, 3 folders (Box 8)
  - Leadership Meeting Notes 1976, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Letters from Hugh Scott, Balliol College, Oxford, England 1967 (Box 8)
  - Memorials 1963-1984 (Box 8)
  - Menu Cards 1959-1982, n.d. (Box 8)
  - Northern Virginia Sun: "Otherwords" 1982-1987 (Box 9)
  - Oral History Interviews with United States Senator Hugh Doggett Scott, Jr. 1978 (Box 9)
  - Oral History Interviews with United States Senator Hugh Scott 1980-1985 (Box 9)
  - The Pacific Rim: 5th Annual International Business Conference, Los Angeles, CA 1982 (Box 9)
  - Personal Writings of Hugh and Marian Scott 1938-1984 (Box 9)
  - Place Cards for Hugh Scott and others n.d. (Box 9)
  - Portrait of Hugh Scott by Chris Owen commissioned for the Hugh Scott Room 1980-1983 (Box 9)
  - Prayers 1952-1972, n.d. (Box 9)
  - Randolph-Macon College 1955-1981 (Box 9)
  - Republican Congressional Wives 1958-1965 (Box 9)
  - Republican National Committee 1948-1949 (Box 9)
  - Republican National Committee Correspondence 1948-1949 (Box 10)
  - Republican National Committee News Releases 1948-1949 (Box 10)
  - Republican National Committee News Releases: Addresses 1948, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Republican National Committee News Releases: Addresses of the Chairman 1948-1949, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Republican National Committee: The Chairman's Letter 1948-1949 (Box 10)
  - Republican National Convention of 1952--notes by Hugh Scott n.d. (Box 10)
  - Republican National Convention of 1972 in San Diego, California 1971-1972 (Box 11)
  - Republican Senatorial Inner Circle 1985 (Box 11)
  - Ripon Society and Bow Group First Transatlantic Conference 1982 (Box 11)
  - Scott Gems 1949(1966-1976)1986 (Box 11)
  - Scott Residences 1959-1976 (Box 11)
  - Senate Appropriations Subcommittee on State, Justice, Commerce, the Judiciary and related agencies 1981-1982 (Box 11)
  - Senate Bicentennial Study Group: Senate Resolution 381 1982 (Box 11)
  - Senate Ethics Committee 1968-1977 (Box 11)
  - Senate Judiciary Subcommittee on the Constitution: Hearing re Senate Joint Resolution 71 1983-1984 (Box 11)
  - "Senate Party Leadership: From the 1950's to the 1980's" by Robert L. Peabody 1980 (Box 12)
  - Smithsonian Institution 1979-1983 (Box 12)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Regents Meetings 1957-1980 [1982] (Box 12)
  - Speeches and Other Writings by Hugh Scott, and related material 1938(1979-1981) (Box 12)
  - Speeches and Other Writings by Hugh Scott, and related material 1982-1986, n.d. (Box 12)
  - "Teas and Towels" by Marian Huntington Chase Scott n.d. (Box 12)
  - Trips: Asia--Hong Kong 1971-1972 (Box 12)
  - Trips: Asia and Europe 1966 (Box 13)
  - Trips: Asia and Europe--Hong Kong, Japan, and Thailand 1966 (Box 13)
  - Trips: Asia and Europe--Italy and Spain 1966 (Box 13)
  - Trips: Asia and Europe--Turkey and Yugoslavia 1966 (Box 13)
  - Trips: Asian and African Continents 1959 (Box 13)
  - Trips: China 1970-1976 (Box 14)
  - Trips: England 1970 (Box 14)
  - Trips: England--Ditchley Foundation Conference 1964-1965, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Trips: England--Interparliamentary Union 1967 (Box 14)
  - Trips: England--London--U.S. Congressional Delegation for Magna Carta Ceremonies 1976, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Trips: Europe and Asia--summary by Hugh Scott 1947 (Box 15)
  - Trips: Europe including the Union of Soviet Socialist Republics 1971, 1975 (Box 15)
  - Trips: Indonesia 1972-1977 (Box 15)
  - Trips: Monaco--Interparliamentary Union Spring Meeting 1970 (Box 15)
  - Trips: Pacific Ocean 1964-1965 (Box 15)
  - Trips: Pacific Ocean--Hawaii, Fiji, French Polynesia, and New Zealand 1964-1965 (Box 15)
  - Trips: Spain--Interparliamentary Union Spring Meeting 1966-1967, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Trips: Spain--Interparliamentary Union Spring Meeting 1966-1967 (Box 16)
  - Trips: Venezuela--Interparliamentary Meeting 1971 (Box 16)
  - United States-Japanese Government Leaders symposium 1982 (Box 16)
  - United States Navy Air Crash at Mimo-Cho, Japan, and related material 1944-1973 (Box 16)
  - The United States Political System Lectures, Balliol College, Oxford, England 1967 (Box 16)
  - U.S.S. Philadelphia 1967-1977, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - "Ups and Dons in Wary Old England" by Marian Huntington Chase Scott 1967 (Box 16)